S/J

Samuel Jones

Programmei

- 281-678-2990
- samuelicjones@gmail.com
- ♥ Tomball / Texas
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/samuel-jones-677b2823b/
- % https://SamuelJones24.github.io/Portfolio

ABOUT ME

Hi, my name is Samuel Jones, and I am a highly motivated and experienced programmer. With 10 years of programming experience throughout my middle school and high school career, I am confident in my ability to tackle any project. In my current role as lead instructor, curriculum creator, and administrator at iCode. I have honed my skills in both teaching and project management.

SKILLS

7 / 10
C++
8 / 10
MySQL
9 / 10
JavaScript
10 / 10
Python
9 / 10
HTML / CSS

EDUCATION

High School Degree

Atlanta High School 2018 - 2022

Associate of Arts

Lone Star Community College 2022 - 2023

EXPERIENCE

Lead Instructor / Curriculum Creator / Administrator

iCode / Cypress Tx / June 2022 – Jan 2023

As a lead instructor, curriculum creator, and administrator at iCode I was responsible for teaching programming courses, developing and updating educational materials, and managing the day-to-day operations of the company.

- Led programming courses for students of all ages and developed and updated corresponding curriculum materials
- Assisted in the management of the company's daily operations, including scheduling, budgeting, hiring, and resource allocation
- Stayed up to date with the latest industry trends and best practices to ensure the quality of coursework and educational materials

Cook

Café Marrese / Tomball Tx / April 2021 – September 2021

As a cook at a French cafe, I was responsible for preparing and executing menu items, managing kitchen inventory and supplies, maintaining a clean and organized workspace, and collaborating to create new dishes.

- Prepared and executed a variety of dishes on the menu, ensuring the highest standards of quality and presentation.
- Managed kitchen inventory to ensure efficient operations
- Maintained a clean and organized workspace, while adhering to strict food safety regulations.